ANDREW VONDERLUFT

DEVELOPER / DEVOPS / SYSADMIN

avonderluft@avlux.net

360.600.9962 Battle Ground, WA United States

Profile

Creative thinker with broad experience in developing and implementing I.T. solutions

Skills

DevOps / SysAdmin

Configuring systems for efficient software deployment

Software Developer

Creating beneficial apps that delight users and maintainers

Musician

Making music with others for collective joy

Technical

DevOps / SysOps	AWS Admin	Capistrano	PostgreSQL	OO Architecture
Deploy Automation	Ruby / Bash	TeamCity, Travis	MySQL, SQLite	MVC design, Rails
CI Engineering	Linux SysAdmin	Puppet	XML, HTML, HAML	Radiant CMS
Config Mgmt	CDN config	JIRA / Redmine	CSS, SASS	JS, JQuery, et al.

Experiences

Renew Financial - https://renewfinancial.com

Jan 2015 - present

DevOps Engineer

Automate, integrate and manage software deployment lifecycle

Configure and manage continuous integration tools and build systems

Provide system resources to Software Development and QA teams

Maintain internal systems to maximize automation and repeatability

Monitor and optimize systems and application performance

Ensure secure operation and configuration of all technical infrastructure

AVLUX Enterprises, LLC - https://avlux.net/

Jul 2000 - present

Principal

Oversee operations for small hosting company, specializing in Git, Subversion, Rails and Redmine

Perform systems and software setup and configuration

Provide customer support

Con-way, Inc. - http://www.con-way.com

Feb 1996 - Jan 2015

Senior Software Engineer

Design, configure and deploy web application infrastructure on Linux and OSX

Configure web application components including Apache, Nginx, Passenger, Bundler, MySQL, DNS

Develop and extend internal and external websites using Ruby, Rails, Redmine, RadiantCMS

Configure and manage Source Control Management using Subversion and Git

Mentor I.T. staff in use of developement tools and technologies

Pacific Data Group - http://www.comsys.us/

Mar 1995 - Feb 1996

Systems Analyst (Contractor)

Lead Analyst for Order Entry Systems - code, test and quality assurance

Job flow dependency analysis and tuning, On-call support

Projects

RadiantCMS - http://radiantcms.org/

2008 - 2014

Core committer. Radiant is a Rails-based, no-fluff, open source content management system

Education

Reed College - http://reed.edu/, Portland, OR U.S.A

1977 - 1981 Classics Languages

English

Native language

Javascript, JQuery

Conversant

Ruby

Delighted disciple

Python, Perl

Acquainted

Bash, PHP, Java

Proficient practitioner

Classical Greek

Competent reader

Links

github -

https://github.com/avonderluft

rubygems -

http://rubygems.org/profiles/avonderluft

<u>linkedin -</u>

http://www.linkedin.com/in/avonderluft

 $And rew \ von der Luft - \underline{avonder luft@avlux.net} - 360.600.9962$